Register of the Herbert Hoover Oral History Program Interviews 1966-1973
Hoover Institution Archives
- TRANSCRIPTS, 1966-1972
  - Strauss, Lewis L. (A.R.A. administrator and very good friend of Herbert Hoover)
  - Stravalli, Cosimo (barber)
  - Strench, Mary M. (daughter of Dr. Minthorn, H.H.'s uncle, who adopted him as a young boy)
  - Stuart, Graham (Stanford University political science professor, Hoover Institution Advisory Board; acquaintance of Herbert Hoover)
  - Stump, Admiral Felix B. (friend of Herbert Hoover, Jr. and acquainted with Herbert Hoover, Sr. through Bohemian Club)
  - Sullivan, Mark, Jr. (father was very good friend of Herbert Hoover) (Box 23)
  - Surface, Anna B. (wife of Frank M. Surface, Assistant Food Administrator, A.R.A.)
  - Swain, Robert C. (neighbor and friend of Allan Hoover)
  - Swim, Dudley (Republican Party activist; Hoover Institution Advisory Board)
  - Sworakowski, Witold S. (Associate Director, Hoover Institution)
  - Taft, Robert, Jr. (son of Ohio Senator Robert Taft, who worked with Herbert Hoover in post-war food relief--political contact)
  - Terman, Frederick E. (Stanford University enginering professor, fellow Bohemian and friend of Herbert Hoover, Jr.)
  - Thayer, Hanford (nephew of Rep. J.H. MacLafferty)
  - Thomas, Lowell (casual friend)
  - Thompson, Mrs. Leon (maid to Mrs. Hoover)
  - Tierney, Nicholas A. (physician in Florida)
  - Timmons, Bascom N. (biographer of John Nance Garner, Minority Leader and Speaker of the House during Hoover Administration)
  - Torrey, Clare M. (C.R.B. and Finnish relief) (Box 24)
  - Treat, Payson J. (Stanford University history professor and acquaintance)
  - Trohan, Walter (casual friend and fellow Bohemian)
  - Trueblood, J. Elton (Stanford University philosophy professor and fellow Quaker)
  - Tuck, Hilda Burge (Mrs. W. Hallam) (Belgian whose father and husband both worked with the C.R.B.)
  - Turner, Scott (mining engineer, friend of T.A. and Edgar Rickard, the latter a very close friend of Herbert Hoover)
  - Tuthill, Marshall W. (A.R.A.)
  - Tyson, Robert C. (Hoover Institution Advisory Board)
  - Vaughan, Gen. Harry H. (aide to President Truman)
  - Wah, Gue Gim (cafe owner in a now-defunct mining community/company in which Herbert Hoover was a major stockholder)
  - Wall, Robert W., Jr. (FBI agent on Latin American trip)
  - Wallace, Lawrence H. (Executive Secretary, American Engineering Council)
  - Waltman, Franklyn (journalist and Public Relations Director, Republican National Committee--minimal acquaintance) (Box 25)
  - Wampler, Cloud (Republican Party activist and casual friend; re: Taft presidential candidacy)
  - Warner, Albert L. (journalist, New York Herald Tribune, during Hoover Administration)
  - Wedemeyer, General Albert C. (occasional White House aide during Hoover Administration, briefed Herbert Hoover on World War II military strategy; fellow Bohemian)
  - Weeks, Sinclair (Secretary of Commerce during Eisenhower Administration, Republican Party activist)
  - Wellington, Laurence C. (C.R.B. and A.R.A.)
  - Wells, Kenneth D. (President, Freedoms Foundation, of which Herbert Hoover was Honorary President)
  - Wheeler, Maynard (consulting physician)
  - White, William L. (journalist and friend)
  - White, Helen H. (parents were at Stanford University with the Hoovers; interviewee later became a secretary to Mrs. Hoover)
  - Wickes, Francis C. (C.R.B. and A.R.A.) (Box 26)
  - Wickett, Fred A. (Mrs. Wickett's parents were friends of the Hoovers; the Wicketts lived in Palo Alto and Mr. Wickett was involved with New York Life Insurance Company)
  - Wilbur, Dwight L. (son of Dr. Ray Lyman Wilbur, close friend of Herbert Hoover; Second Hoover Commission)
  - Wilbur, Ray L., Jr. (son of Dr. Ray Lyman Wilbur)
  - Willis, Mildred Hoover (niece of Herbert Hoover)
  - Wilson, Richard (journalist and fellow Bohemian)
  - Wolfe, Henry C. (A.R.A. in Russia; author who occasionally discussed international relations with Herbert Hoover)
  - Wolfe, Preston (journalist whose father and uncle were active in the 1928 presidential campaign--minimal personal contact)
  - Yeager, Naomi (secretary to Herbert Hoover)
  - Young, Clarence M. (Asst. Sec. for Aeronautics in Commerce Department under H.H.)
- PHONOTAPES, 1965-1968. (Tape cabinet)
  Sound recordings of interviews and a speech by President Lyndon Johnson. Arranged alphabetically by name of speaker.
  - Clark (Birge) interview, 1968 July 2 (Reel 1)
    Birge, an architect, talks about the Herbert Hoover family and Stanford University. Use copy reference number: xx028_a_0008069
  - Clark (Esther) interview, 1968 July 30 (Reel 2)
    Dr. Rita R. Campbell interviews Dr. Clark concerning Herbert Hoover at Stanford University, and the Hoover home. Use copy reference number: xx028_a_0008068
  - Johnson (President Lyndon B.) remarks at the signing ceremony for the Herbert Hoover Historical Site 1965 August 12 (Reel 3)
    Johnson speaks in the Rose Garden on the occasion of his signing into law the bill for the Herbert Hoover Historical Site, West Branch. Johnson gives his thoughts about Hoover as a man, as a president, and as a presidential adviser. Use copy reference number: xx028_a_0008067